mercurypay.com 2019-09-12

# Worldpay Privacy Policy, Copyright Notices & Terms of Use | Worldpay

Click here to adjust your Cookie Settings

Introduction

Data Protection Officer contact details.

What Personal Information does Worldpay collect?

For what purposes does Worldpay use Personal Information?

With whom does Worldpay share Personal Information and for what purposes?

Use of Worldpay family of websites.

Links to third party sites and public posting.

Information on cross-border data transfers.

Individual’s Privacy Rights (data subject rights)

How does Worldpay ensure the security of Personal Information?

How long does Worldpay store and retain Personal Information?

Any questions?

## Introduction

Worldpay, Inc. (together with its subsidiaries, collectively “Worldpay” or “we”) recognizes and respects the privacy of individuals whose Personal Information it collects and otherwise processes in the course of conducting business. We are committed to ensuring that we process Personal Information in accordance with applicable privacy laws and regulations and this Privacy Notice.

This Privacy Notice applies to the Personal Information, Including Personal Data, processed in relation to current, prospective and former Worldpay customers, cardholders who transact with our customers (including individuals who maintain a card with one of our financial institution clients), job applicants and current and former Worldpay colleagues.

This Privacy Notice (together with Worldpay’s terms of use and any other documents referred to herein) sets out the basis on which any Personal Information Worldpay collects, uses, shares and otherwise processes. Please read the following carefully to understand Worldpay’s views and practices regarding Personal Information and how Worldpay will treat it. By accessing and using Worldpay Services, including Worldpay’s interactions with you via our websites, mobile sites and applications (“ **Sites and Services** ”),you agree to the processing of Personal Information as set out in this Privacy Notice.

When Worldpay uses the word ‘card’ in this Privacy Notice, it applies to all payment methods and types and not simply those involving a physical card; and use of the term ‘cardholder’ applies to any shopper or individual whose payment transactions may be processed.

This Privacy Notice is global in scope, but is not intended to override any legal rights in any territory where such rights prevail. In such event, the rights and obligations set out in this Privacy Notice will apply, subject only to amendment under any applicable local law having precedence.

## Data Protection Officer contact details

Worldpay’s global headquarters is based in Cincinnati, Ohio, United States, and its international headquarters is based in London, United Kingdom. Worldpay has appointed a Data Protection Officer for you to contact if you have any questions or concerns about Worldpay’s Personal Information policies or practices. Worldpay’s Data Protection Officer and contact information are as follows:

**Data Protection Officer**

Worldpay

The Walbrook building

25 Walbrook

London

EC4N 8AF

## What Personal Information does Worldpay collect?

Worldpay collects Personal Information relating to cardholders, merchants or other customers, suppliers and other business partners in order to carry out its business activities. Worldpay may collect Personal Information from various sources, including:

  * Information you voluntarily provide, either directly or via our customers;
  * Information automatically collected when you use our Sites and Services, including in our role as a payment processor;
  * Information collected by cookies and other tracking technologies when you use our Sites; and
  * Information collected from third parties, including fraud monitoring providers, commercial databases, or know your customer ( **KYC** ) providers.

This Personal Information may include:

  * Contact information
  * Demographic information
  * National Identification information
  * Merchant or other Customer identification
  * Merchant or other Customer management
  * Payment transaction information
  * Financial and credit card information
  * Credit risk information
  * Technical information
  * Applications

  * **Contact information** , including: name (first, last and business), telephone numbers, address (home, billing and business), fax, email address and other communications;
  * **Demographic information** , including: nationality, country of residence, date of birth, marital status, birth place, gender, preferred language, citizenship;
  * **National Identification information** , such as: national insurance number, passport, social security number, taxpayer identification number, driver license or other form of identification to verify the cardholder, customer or potential candidate;
  * **Monitoring or Recording** , including: monitoring or recording telephone calls, emails, web chats, CCTV, access control or other communications;
  * **Merchant or other Customer identification** , such as: merchant or customer ID;
  * **Merchant or other Customer management,** including billing, invoicing, refunds, reconciliations and reporting;
  * **Points or rewards received,** for example through a loyalty scheme;
  * **Information related to items purchased** , including: location of the purchase, value, time, method, any feedback that is given in relation to such purchase;
  * **Payment transaction information** , including: Alternative Payment Methods (“ **APMs** ”), transaction monitoring, fraud monitoring, products/services, trend analysis, analytics;
  * **Financial and credit card information** , including: payment account number (PAN) or account number, card expiration date, CVC details, bank and/or issuer details;
  * **Credit risk information** , including: information obtained about you from credit reference or fraud prevention agencies, credit history, credit score, fraud monitoring;
  * **HR information,** including:information which you provide in a job application form or any other information obtained or provided by you during the course of your registration and application and email alerts of future vacancies;
  * **Technical information** , including: the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer or device to the Internet, your device ID, login information (username/password), browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, device operating system platform, mobile carrier, location or GPS/geo-location;
  * **Information about your visit or whether you opened an email** , including: the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from Worldpay’s site (including date and time), products or services you viewed or searched for page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from the site page, any phone number used to call Worldpay’s customer service number;
  * **Photographs and videos of you,** from Worldpay events, through identity verification or as part of an interview;
  * **Publically accessible comments and opinions** reviewed and used by Worldpay, through Internet searches or posted on social networking sites, such as Facebook and LinkedIn;
  * **Insights** gained through Worldpay gatherings from sessions that you participate in and contribute at Worldpay events(anonymized basis);
  * **Social media posts** on Worldpay social media sites or made publically about Worldpay on social media **;**
  * **Event participant** **details** from a Worldpay event, including: name, title and company from a Worldpay app for the event which is available to registered delegates; and
  * **Applications** , if you download or use mobile or desktop applications, including information about your location, your device or the service you are using (including where a payment transaction takes place).

## For what purposes does Worldpay use Personal Information?

Worldpay uses Personal Information internally in relation to its main processing activities, which are categorized as follows:

  * **Operations**
  * **Risk Management**
  * **Transaction Processing**
  * **Marketing**
  * **Relationship Management**
  * **Products**

Worldpay uses Personal Information for purposes that are appropriate, based on legitimate interests or as authorized by applicable law. These purposes may include:

  * **Legal, regulatory or law enforcement purposes**
  * **HR purposes**
  * **Credit risk purposes**
  * **Fraud monitoring purposes**
  * **Security purposes**
  * **Marketing purposes**
  * **Product development purposes**
  * **Customer Service/Account Management purposes**

  * **Operations** , which includes: IT, telephony, security and analytics services;
  * **Risk Management** , which includes: fraud mitigation and management, authentication and acceptance;
  * **Transaction Processing** , which includes: compliance monitoring, scheme operations, disputes/chargebacks, capturing payments, settlement, gateway services, pre-paid card processing and program management and authorization;
  * **Marketing** , which includes: customer acquisition, usage analysis, lead generation and cross-sell/upsell;
  * **Relationship Management** , which includes: supplier relationship management, credit risk monitoring and customer relationship management; and
  * **Products** , which includes: data analytics, business finance, self-service, fraud service, foreign exchange service, currency services, as well as the development of new products.

**Legal, regulatory or law enforcement purposes:**

  * Comply with local and national laws, including card scheme rules and requests from law enforcement and regulatory authorities;
  * Enforce our legal rights and satisfy our legal obligations, including, without limitation, any reporting or disclosure obligations under applicable law or regulations or subpoena, court order or other judicial or administrative process, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is legally required or otherwise necessary to protect our rights and property, or the rights, property or safety of others;
  * Conduct our own due diligence checks;
  * Prevent, detect and prosecute fraud or crime or to assist others in doing so;
  * Assist in investigation by Worldpay, other financial organizations or third parties of suspected criminal activity;
  * Carry out obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and Worldpay;
  * Manage and enforce Worldpay’s rights, terms of use or any other contracts with you and your business;
  * Assess financial and insurance risks;
  * Notify you about important changes or developments to Worldpay’s website or Worldpay’s goods and services;
  * Recover debt or in relation to your insolvency, including tracing your whereabouts;
  * Identify and monitor for fraud;
  * Maintain internal recordkeeping and reporting;
  * Prepare and furnish compilations and analyses as well as other reports of aggregated and anonymized information;
  * Check your personal or business credit status/profile and identity; and
  * Record and track details of your transactions or your customer’s transactions.

**HR purposes:**

  * Process your job application if you apply for a job vacancy at Worldpay;
  * Register and send you email alerts of future vacancies; and
  * Maintain internal recordkeeping and reporting.

**Credit risk purposes:**

  * Conduct our own due diligence checks;
  * Check your personal or business credit status/profile and identity;
  * Record and track details of your transactions or your customer’s transactions;
  * Maintain internal recordkeeping and reporting;
  * Identify and monitor for fraud;
  * Assess financial and insurance risks;
  * Mitigate information security, sector or credit risk; and
  * Commercial purposes, such as trend analysis and the use of data analytics to obtain learnings and insight around cardholder transaction patterns and usage.

**Fraud monitoring purposes:**

  * Monitor merchant or other customer transactions in an effort to detect and prevent  fraud;
  * Maintain internal recordkeeping and reporting;
  * Prepare and furnish compilations and analyses as well as other reports of aggregated and anonymized information; and
  * Provide or develop more innovative and effective fraud monitoring services for our merchants or other customers.

**Security purposes:**

  * Conduct our own due diligence checks;
  * Administer Worldpay’s Site and Services for internal operations, including troubleshooting;
  * Keep Worldpay’s Sites and Services safe and secure;
  * Maintain internal recordkeeping and reporting;
  * Identify and monitor for fraud; and
  * Mitigate information security, sector or credit risk.

**Marketing purposes:**

  * Marketing or market research;
  * Perform analysis and comparisons;
  * Maintain internal recordkeeping and reporting;
  * Manage Worldpay gatherings;
  * Improve and develop Worldpay’s business;
  * Provide information about products and services you requested, purchased or which may be of interest to you to ;
  * Provide or develop more innovative and effective Worldpay services for our merchants or other customers;
  * When Worldpay communicates with you or each other;
  * Enable contest, promotion or survey entries;
  * Create profiles and marketing opportunities;
  * Create promotional materials for future events and distribute to event participants;
  * Social media site integration and interaction;
  * Optimize Worldpay’s websites/portals, products and services;
  * Notify you about important changes or developments to Worldpay’s Sites and Services or Worldpay’s goods and services;
  * Improve Worldpay’s Sites and Services, and ensure content is presented in effective way;
  * Allow you to participate in interactive features of Worldpay’s service;
  * Enable you to participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on Worldpay’s Sites and Services; and
  * Obtain your views on goods, services and Worldpay’s Sites and Services.

**Product development purposes:**

  * Provide or develop more innovative, user friendly and effective products and services;
  * Maintain internal recordkeeping and reporting;
  * Prepare and furnish compilations and analyses as well as other reports of aggregated and anonymized information;
  * Commercial purposes, such as trend analysis and the use of data analytics to obtain learnings and insight around cardholder transaction patterns and usage; and
  * Better understand card usage patterns or to optimize your experience.

**Customer Services/Account Management purposes:**

  * Enable you to contact us;
  * Provide training;
  * Provide or develop more innovative and effective Worldpay services for our merchants or other customers;
  * Authorize and establish commercial merchant accounts;
  * Maintain internal recordkeeping and reporting;
  * Enable you to upload and/or store information;
  * Information, products and services you requested, purchased or which may be of interest to you;
  * Enable you to participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on Worldpay’s site;
  * Facilitate collection or redemption of points or rewards currency of any Loyalty program;
  * Manage, investigate and resolve complaints;
  * Obtain your views on goods, services and Worldpay’s website(s);
  * Allow you to participate in interactive features of Worldpay’s service;
  * Respond to any inquires;
  * Enable you to enter a competition, promotion or survey;
  * Provide Worldpay Services to you and your business;
  * Enable you to report a problem with Worldpay’s site;
  * Analyze and report on you or your customers’ use of any Loyalty service;
  * Manage disputes of transactions, rewards or points;
  * Subscribe you to a Worldpay service;
  * Register your use of any Worldpay Services;
  * Process your application for Worldpay Services;
  * Understand Worldpay’s customers' requirements; and
  * Notify you about important changes or developments to Worldpay’s website or Worldpay’s goods and services.

## With whom does Worldpay share Personal Information and for what purposes?

Worldpay may share Personal Information with members of our corporate family, which means our subsidiaries and our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries. We may also share Personal Information with Worldpay-approved third parties for lawful purposes, such as legal and regulatory purposes, in order to deliver and develop our and our partners’ business products and services, and in relation to mergers and acquisitions.

Before we share Personal Information, we ensure there are adequate safeguards in place to protect the processing of that data. Except where permitted, Worldpay does not sell, rent, share or otherwise disclose Personal Information to third parties for the third party’s commercial purposes.

Worldpay does not disclose information that could identify you personally to anyone, except as described in this Privacy Notice, including, but not limited to:

  * Any Worldpay group company;
  * Any group company (such as advisers, share plan, payroll and other third party administrators, agents or contractors working on behalf of Worldpay);
  * Financial institution clients;
  * Service providers and other third parties under contract who help with our business operations (including, but not limited to, fraud investigations, site analytics and operations);
  * Regulatory authorities, such as the UK’s Financial Conduct Authority (“FCA”), Data Protection Authorities, the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau;
  * Social media sites integrated into web services that we offer;
  * Governmental or quasi-governmental organizations; and
  * Potential purchasers of Worldpay.

Worldpay may disclose Personal Information to third parties for the following purposes:

  * **Legal or regulatory purposes**
  * **Business purposes**
  * **Suppliers who assist Worldpay with the provision of its services**

**Legal or regulatory purposes, including:**

  * Where Worldpay are required or permitted to do so by law or regulations, including for tax purposes or to comply with financial services regulations;
  * Where Worldpay deem it in the national interest or otherwise lawful to do so;
  * In the course of litigation;
  * Following requests from governmental or public authorities;
  * National security;
  * As part of a legal process; and
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is legally required or otherwise necessary to protect our rights and property, or the rights, property or safety of others.

**Business purposes, including:**

  * Improve and develop Worldpay’s business;
  * Business partners (including those in which Worldpay has an investment), suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract Worldpay may enter into with them or you;
  * Transfer information and/or assets in the event of a merger, acquisition, sale, bankruptcy filing, or other corporate restructuring;
  * If Worldpay or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case Personal Information held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets; and
  * If Worldpay sells or buys any business or assets, in which case Worldpay may disclose your Personal Information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

**Suppliers who assist Worldpay with the provision of its services, including:**

  * Fulfilling or processing orders or application forms i.e. for job vacancies;
  * Processing payments;
  * Managing credit, security, sector and fraud risk;
  * Market research; and
  * Survey activities.

Where Worldpay uses and/or discloses confidential or cardholder transactional data for preparing and furnishing compilations, analyses and other reports of aggregated information and anonymized information, it will do so provided it has taken reasonable measures to avoid identifying any customer of Worldpay other than the customer whose transactions were involved in the preparation of any compilation, analysis or other report. This data may be used for statistical, analytic, and administrative purposes, including for customizing our Sites and Services, analyzing trends, tailoring products and services, or conducting risk and cost analysis.

## Use of Worldpay family of websites

Worldpay’s websites use “cookies” and other technologies, which store small amounts of information on your computer or device to allow certain information from your web browser to be collected.

Cookies (and similar technologies) are widely used on the internet and allow a website/portal to recognize a user’s device, without uniquely identifying the individual person using the computer.

For more information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage, block and delete them, see www.allaboutcookies.org and Worldpay’s Cookies Policy. You may also be able to configure your browser not to accept cookies, although please note this may affect your ability to use the services Worldpay provides.

Worldpay respects the privacy of children and encourages all parents to supervise their children’s computer usage. We do not knowingly collect or retain Personal Information from children under the age of 18. To learn more about the Children’s Online Privacy Protect Act (COPPA) please visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website at [http://www.business.ftc.gov/privacy-and-security/children's-privacy](https://www.ftc.gov/tips-advice/business-center/privacy-and-security/children%27s-privacy).

Cookies (and similar technologies) are widely used on the internet and allow a website/portal to recognise a user’s device, without uniquely identifying the individual person using the computer. These technologies help to make it easier for you to log on and use the website, provide feedback to Worldpay as to which parts of the website you visit or viewing preferences from a previous use of our website when you return to our website, so Worldpay can assess the effectiveness of the website or communication, to provide a better user experience or to serve Worldpay advertisements to you while browsing other websites. Worldpay may also use the aggregate information from these technologies to research and understand how the Sites and Services are used.

Some web browsers may send out ‘do not track’ signals. There is no industry standard currently in place as to what websites and other online services should do upon receipt of such signals. Should such a standard be developed, Worldpay will re-visit its Privacy Notice, but currently takes no action upon receipt of such signals.

Worldpay may offer certain features that are only available through the use of tracking technologies. Temporary cookies are used to enable you to navigate our site and use its features. These are deleted when you close your browser. IP addresses are used in conjunction with cookies for the purpose of “remembering” computers or other devices used to access our site.

Analytical or performance cookies collect anonymous information about how visitors use our websites. They allow us to analyse information such as the count of visitors to our websites, what search terms our visitors are using, what pages are viewed, and the last page visited. This information is based on the visitor’s IP address, and we cannot view individual activity tied to a single person.

Under this Privacy Notice, information collected by cookies and similar technologies are dealt with as Non-Personal Information. To the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses (or similar identifiers) are clearly defined to be Personal Information under any local law and where such local law is applicable to Worldpay Services, Worldpay will manage such identifiers as Personal Information.

## Links to third party sites and public posting

Worldpay’s websites may also contain links to and from third party websites, including those of partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow such a link or if you post information or content, such as commenting on content or participating in online forums or communities, or when you interact with our websites through social media sites, plug-ins or other applications, depending on your privacy settings, this information may become public on the Internet. Please note that these websites have their own privacy notices and cookies policies, and Worldpay does not accept any responsibility or liability for these third party websites.

If our websites link through to third party websites, those processes may involve the placement of third party cookies on your machine or device. Please be aware that we do not control these third party websites or any of the content contained on those websites, including the third-party cookies used for these purposes. The inclusion of links to third party websites in no way constitutes an endorsement by us of such websites’ content, actions, or policies.

We may also, from time to time, partner with ad networks and other online advertising providers in order to serve ads on behalf of us or other non-affiliated parties on our websites and across the Internet. These ads may be presented to you based on products and services the advertising providers think are relevant to your interests. These preferences may be inferred based on information collected about your browsing behavior on our websites and other non-affiliated websites and apps across time. We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (“ **DAA** ”) Self-Regulatory Principles. To learn more about, or opt-out of, this type of advertising from participants in the DAA, you can visit www.aboutads.info.

## Information on cross-border data transfers

Worldpay has its global headquarters in Cincinnati, Ohio, United States, and its international headquarters in London, United Kingdom. Information Worldpay collects from you may be transferred, stored and processed in a country different from where the data was collected or outside of the European Economic Area (“ **EEA** ”), for example, data collected from within the EEA may be stored or processed in the United States or data collected from the United States may be stored or processed in India or Asia Pacific (Philippines).

Worldpay eCommerce complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data received from the European Union (EU) and Switzerland to the United States. Please click _here_ to view our Worldpay eCommerce Privacy Shield Policy.

Paymetric complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data received from the European Union (EU) to the United States. Please click _here_ to view our Paymetric Privacy Shield Policy.

By using our Worldpay Sites and Services, you are permitting the transfer of Personal Information to Worldpay in the United States, which has different data protection laws that the EU and Switzerland have not deemed equivalent to those in EU member countries and Switzerland. The transfer of information will often be in furtherance of a contract to which you are a party. In other cases, the transfer of information will be consistent with the legitimate interests of Worldpay eCommerce. In other cases, we rely on your consent to the transfer of this information for the uses described in our Privacy Shield Policies and in this Privacy Notice to the extent permitted by EU and Swiss laws.

Worldpay or such other third party service providers may also process payments through other financial institutions. These external organizations may process and store your Personal Information abroad and Worldpay may have to disclose your information to foreign authorities to help them in their fight against crime and terrorism. Where these organizations are based outside the EEA and Switzerland, your Personal Information may not be protected to the same standards.

Worldpay also provides contact center services outside of the EEA and Switzerland.

## Individual’s Privacy Rights (data subject rights)

Under the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation, individuals located in Europe are able to exercise rights regarding their Personal Information. You can find a more detailed summary of these rights on the Information Commissioner’s Office’s website [here](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr). These rights include:

  * the right to access;
  * the right to rectification;
  * the right to restriction;
  * the right to erasure;
  * the right to object; and
  * the right to data portability.

If your request cannot be provided within the required time frame, Worldpay will provide you with a date when the information will be provided. If your request is denied, Worldpay will provide an explanation as to why it has been denied.

Individuals in Andorra, Argentina, Australia, Canada, Faroe Islands, Guernsey, Hong Kong, Israel, Isle of Man, Japan, Jersey, Mexico, New Zealand, Singapore, South Korea, Switzerland, Uruguay, and certain other jurisdictions may also exercise these or similar rights.

California’s “Shine The Light” law permits California residents free of charge to annually request and obtain a list of certain categories of Personal Information disclosed to third- parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the names and addresses of such third parties and such further information sufficient to give the customer a reasonable indication of the nature of the third parties' business. Please send any such request to the contact address below, and Worldpay will respond within 30 days.

The laws of other territories applicable to your dealings with Worldpay may also be relevant (and may also impact the above rights). Any such rights can be progressed through our customer services center or via the ‘contact us’ section below. However, all cardholder requests must first be directed to the relevant customer. Worldpay will assist customers with such requests accordingly.

## How does Worldpay ensure the security of Personal Information?

Worldpay works to maintain your confidence and trust in us and has therefore implemented physical, technical, and administrative measures designed to secure Personal Information from accidental loss, unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. However, the safety and security of your information is also dependent upon you. We store and process your information on our servers located within the United Kingdom and the United States and use other computing facilities around the globe.

Where Worldpay has given you (or where you have chosen) a password or access code which enables you to access certain parts of Worldpay’s website/portal or mobile applications and similar, you are responsible for keeping this password and/or access code confidential. You should not share your password or access code with anyone and you should use all reasonable methods to ensure that there is no unauthorized use. You therefore authorize Worldpay to act upon instructions and information received from any person that enters your user ID and password and you agree to be fully responsible for all use and any actions that may take place during the use of your account. You also agree to promptly notify Worldpay of any information you have provided which has changed.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although Worldpay will take reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information, Worldpay cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to Worldpay’s site; any transmission is at your own risk.

Worldpay maintains security standards that are designed to protect your information as it is transmitted from your computer to our network. This technology is called Secure Socket Layer (SSL). SSL is a leading security protocol for data transfer on the Internet and helps to protect the safety and confidentiality of your online banking information.

You have a role in helping Worldpay by safeguarding your information from others. You have several options when deciding how you can best protect your Personal Information. One option is simply not to volunteer it. The Federal Trade Commission’s websites (www.ftc.gov, www.ftc.gov/idtheft, and www.onguardonline.gov) offer useful information about how to protect your Personal Information.

## How long does Worldpay store and retain Personal Information?

Worldpay will store Personal Information only for the greater of as long as necessary to achieve the purposes for which it was collected and as required by applicable law. Retention periods for transaction and other data categories may vary, depending on our obligations. For example, legal and regulatory compliance with anti-money laundering (AML) and KYC requirements, operational demands, business requirements or dates we assigned based on contracts will also need to be taken into account, and may require retention for a period of up to 7 years after the data was collected or after the merchant or other customer relationship has ended.

**Changes and updates to the Privacy Notice**

Worldpay may, from time to time, make changes to this Privacy Notice. If any material changes are made as to how Worldpay treat Personal Information, you will be notified through this Privacy Notice on Worldpay’s Sites and Services.

The date the Privacy Notice was last modified is at the bottom of the page. You are responsible for ensuring you periodically visit our Sites and Services and Privacy Notice to check for any changes. By continuing to use Worldpay Services, you agree to the changes in this Privacy Notice.

## Any questions?

All comments, queries and requests relating to Worldpay’s use of Personal Information are welcomed. Please contact Worldpay’s Data Protection Officer:

**Data Protection Officer**

Worldpay  
The Walbrook building  
25 Walbrook  
London  
EC4N 8AF  
privacyoffice@worldpay.com

If you are in the United Kingdom and have any queries or complaints about the processing of your Personal Information, you can also contact the Information Commissioner’s Office [here](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/).

If you are in the United States and have any queries or complaints about the processing of your Personal Information, you can also contact the Federal Trade Commission [ here](http://www.ftc.gov/).
